[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 24, "question": "What's it like to give away $1 billion?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "$", "CD", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 25, "answer": "You can't do it very often.", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$1 billion"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "Are you nervous?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "A little bit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "What is going on in America right now that is preventing more Tyler Perrys coming through, because clearly, they're not coming through in the same number?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "IN", "VBZ", "VBG", "JJR", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "IN", ",", "IN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "Well, I think it's just, if you look at the country and then you look at what we came out of, you know, and this is with the administration before this, it was very, very difficult.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tyler Perrys"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", ",", "CC", "DT", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "POS", "IN", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "CC", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "CC", "JJ", "CC", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NNS", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "TO", "VB", "NN", "RB", ",", "NN", "NN", ",", "NN", "JJ", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 69, "question": "What is your advice for 23 million other Americans who are currently out of work and want a job?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "CD", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 70, "answer": "Well, for me, I -- I can tell you this, and this may not be good advice for every person that's out of work, but for a lot of people, what I've found, and even when I was going through and homeless and trying to find a job and all those things, sometimes it means that you ought to try something else, something different, something new, because there were times in my life where I lost a lot.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "What do you think is going to happen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "I'm not actually looking forward to the third one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "RB", ":", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "WRB", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBZ", "NN", "CC", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 99, "question": "Why is it getting so fractured?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 100, "answer": "Well, unfortunately, I just -- being in the business that I'm in, which is show business, I realize that a lot of things is smoke and mirrors, a lot of this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "What did you think of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "Well, I think it's awful that -- that it happened.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 162, "question": "Can any president deserve four more years if those two big figures loom large for the electorate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CD", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 163, "answer": "ERRY: Well, I think about it this way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "Is America more or less racist after four years of its first black president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "RBR", "CC", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "That's very interesting question.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 187, "question": "Is that helpful?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "I don't -- first of all, I don't think it's healthy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "VBN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "He had been abused?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "Oh, abused his entire life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 229, "question": "How did you find this out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "I found it out by asking questions, finally, of him, because I was talking to him --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 231, "question": "So, he told you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 232, "answer": "He told me a lot about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "Is he still alive, your father?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "Yes, he's still alive.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "And what kind of relationship do you have with him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "We don't speak very much, but I am taking care of him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 247, "question": "You support him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 248, "answer": "Absolutely, 100 percent.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "Do you think despite the way that he -- he manhandled you and beat you and so on, did you feel that he loved you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "No, I never felt that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", ",", "WDT", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "-- so that was another thing I didn't know, which caused a lot of issues, as well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "WRB", "."], "qSentId": 259, "question": "Did you have that out with him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 260, "answer": "I did, about four years ago I asked, why.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "Has he ever said sorry?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "No, he hasn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 267, "question": "Would you like him to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 268, "answer": "At this point, I don't know if it matters.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "She -- it -- well, you mean of all the success?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "-- get her a red Jaguar?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Jaguar"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "What did she say to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "Just -- she's speechless, just a thank you and the love.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "Who you think you're talking to, old lady?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "You don't know me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 360, "question": "ORGAN: Did you ever think, when you were young and you -- you thought of treading the boards that one day you'd be world famous for cross dressing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "Yes, never --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "There are lots of other Madeas from every -- I've met a Jewish Madea, I've met an Italian Madea, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "IN", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "It's about strong women.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 415, "question": "Any comment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 419, "question": "You feel uncomfortable talking about money?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 420, "answer": "I just try -- it drives me insane.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "WP", "NNS", "TO", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "-- show off about it?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "No, who wants to show -- it's not a -- it's certainly not about showing off.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", ":", "WDT", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "What is the best thing about money, though, for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "Again, the best thing which is -- which changed my entire life was being able to support my mother.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 462, "question": "Why do you -- why do you feel awkward talking about this kind of thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 463, "answer": "Because I just feel that to whom much is given, much is required.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "How have you avoided the pitfalls that go with superstar fame, big money and all the rest of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "My faith.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tyler"]}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "How do you know that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "I know everything, Tyler.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "You supplied the plane, didn't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tyler"]}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "What is this, that this woman's life is not worth a moment of silence?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "Take another break, Tyler.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "Do you enjoy playing the action hero?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "I actually did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Oprah"]}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "What does that mean?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "That's what Oprah said to me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "EX", "VBP"], "qSentId": 576, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "Because there are", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 588, "question": "And what went wrong?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "I think we were both very young.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 596, "question": "Was it, in the end, your decision to walk away?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 597, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 599, "question": "Do you regret that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 600, "answer": "No, I don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "IN", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 601, "question": "You thought it was the right thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 602, "answer": "Yeah, because we both were in a place where -- I just realized I should not have said this because -- I should not have said this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 604, "question": "Why shouldn't you have said it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 605, "answer": "Because I said too much.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 632, "question": "What's the rush?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 633, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 637, "question": "Don't you want little Tylers running around?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 638, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 652, "question": "Do you want a glass of water?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 653, "answer": "I need a shot of vodka, my friend.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 679, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 680, "answer": "I'm fine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 685, "question": "Who do you think's going to win?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "POS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 686, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 691, "question": "Are you surprised how powerful television has now become?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 692, "answer": "I'd say a little bit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 695, "question": "Does he deserve a second term?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 696, "answer": "If he gets elected.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 700, "question": "Has he done enough, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 701, "answer": "For me, he has.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 704, "question": "What do you want to see from whoever wins in three weeks time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 705, "answer": "I want to see the best man win.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 723, "question": "How can a president smartly revive things do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 724, "answer": "Well, I think we spend to much money on the military.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBD", ",", "JJR", "IN", "RB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 762, "question": "Pretty extraordinary thing to have done, to give a billion dollars of your own money away, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 763, "answer": "What it did was, more than just itself, it set a precedent for so many other people to give money while they are young and vibrant and alive, not after they die.", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["a billion dollars"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["United Nations"]}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 774, "question": "What should America be doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "NNP", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 775, "answer": "I think the global policeman should be the United Nations.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 781, "question": "That's shocking, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 782, "answer": "Well, what -- no, I think it's -- I think it's good, because it's so clear that we're programmed and we're born to love and help each other, not to kill each other, to destroy each other.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121019pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 793, "question": "Are you pleased with how the money is being used?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 794, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]